[FAST FORWARD]
Well!
Awww!
Aww...
Yakiniku!
Here we come!
Yay!
I'm starving!
Let's order right away!
Me, Jasmine.
I'm Calpis.
Always Calpis, right? Yes, I do.
Oh, hey...
Shit.
I think I made a mistake.
Go! Just go!
Please.
What's in the assortment of grilled vegetables?
Onions, green peppers, shiitake mushrooms, young corn and green onions.
I'll have that, please.
It has shiitake mushrooms!
May I have this?
Shiitake shiitake shiitake shiitake!
It's got shiitake!
Here we go.
LOL!
Asachi...
You're always like this even if you don't get a towel.
Oh, I see.
Poor Asachi.
LOL!LOL.
And it's kind of a funny story.
I don't think I ever will.
You've been there before.
I have.
I don't know.
You ate there.
Yes, we did.
We were the second place we went, right?
Oh, yeah...
We went to eat Japanese sashimi.
And then we decided to eat some more.
And then we finally went to a restaurant.
The inside is...
Oh, it's delicious!
I'll have a cup of zasmin tea first.
I'll have some.
Isn't it pretty there?
Oh, my God, it's beautiful.
It's like a flower.
Look at that.
Look! You have no idea.
You have no idea.
Look at this!
You want to go that far?
No, I'm gonna stick with it.
I'll tell you what.
I'll take this.
Look!
It's a flower.
Flowers.
Let's get started.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
All right, don't forget.
That's it.The End
I'll try, OYA
I didn't think that the aquarium would really... come true.
Hey, I'm so happy!
I want to go to Edo! I want to go to the aquarium and eat and walk around!
I said I wanted to go to the aquarium and eat and walk around, and it came true!
I'm so happy!
I was asked what I wanted to eat with food. He asked me what I wanted to eat.
I said, "Meat!
I said meat, and it came true!
I'm going to cut lunch.
Okay, how about overflowing yukke?
Overflowing yukke!
You said you wanted yukke.
Yukke!
I want five of them.
She said she wanted yukke.
Yukke!
Pello-Pello-Pello!
LOL!
Looks delicious!
You're shining so brightly.
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle!
Want some?
I'll mix it.
Wow.
It's a waterfall.
Egg waterfall.
Here it comes.
Yum.
It's good.
I could drink that.
Yum!
Um... Um...YUM!!!
If it's on top of rice...
Mmmm!
Bowl of rice topped with meat and hands
It is now complete. This is thinly sliced Sumijiro.
Nice!
This is Sumijiro.
Bread and Otabe!
Wow! It's a work of art!
It's a nice touch!
I liked it all.
Really?
But I didn't laugh twice.
And the cooking, Ichi...
Wow, that's nice!
Are you a baker or a cook? Or do you like to have someone cook for you?
I don't cook if there is someone to cook for me.
I see.
I'm the type of person who doesn't grill either.
Two years old.
How much do you like it grilled?
Well baked? Rare dough?
Lately, I've been getting them rare.
Oh, really?
No.
Oh, thank you!
It's a little thicker when it's baked.
Oh, yeah, that's good!
You can have it.
You're brimming.
Brizzled?
Yeah.
Bling bling?
Yeah, yeah.
Is that bad? Expression.
You know, like, normal pre-preparedness.You know, like a regular pre-prep or something.
Oh, pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre.
Satori yan
Ugh!
Please add hot water if you can.
Yes, thank you.
Wait, first of all, vegetables.
Ha-ha-ha, first of all.
Look, shiitake mushrooms.
You did it!
Two shiitake mushrooms!
I'm so happy!
Shiitake mushrooms, shiitake mushrooms!
And, ta-da!
SATOBURI Ya!
Yaaaay!
It's clumping!
It's amazing!
It's well baked!
Yogurt
Is it a comic book?
Is it a cartoon?
Yeah.
You're happy to eat more food?
Let me eat it.
Mm-hmm.
I'm jealous.
It's good.
Should we celebrate?
Yeah, I do.
Oh, my God!
Meat!
She's beautiful!
I love beautiful women.I love beautiful women.
Ken, you're so busy taking pictures, you've left this room.
Oh, my God, they're all gone around here.
Oh, man!
This is so much fun!
Hey!
Oh, you want to pick it up?
I'll pick it up.
I like it.
I love it!
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, it's good.
Very strong and tasty.
I didn't eat it.
You can tell by the way it goes in your mouth.
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
It's like roast beef.
I thought so.
I'm going to have some.
It's so tender.
Oh!
Yum!
Now it's burning.
Bon appétit.
It's hot.
Mmm?
Soft!
Hey, it's soft.
Mmm!
Looks good on peppers.
Do I look good with green peppers?Do I look good with green peppers?
What's this?
Mmm-hmm.
I have an image that bell peppers are for fashionable people.
No way!
Really?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Look, they're burnt.
Burnt!
Burnt, I'll eat
Burnt, I eat.
I eat.
Scorch, I'll eat.
It's open right now.
Why are you eating burnt?
I'll have a scorch.
Thanks.
Do you want to grill some chitake?
Do you have any tips on how to cook them?
No! Grill them any way you like!
Okay, okay!
Vegetables are sweet.
The vegetables are sweet.
But they're burnt.
You can take it out of my hand and go home.
Oh?
Hi, Mom.
Mama's barbecue.
It's like volleyball.
It's a mama san yakiniku today.
It's a mom-and-pop barbecue today.
We both decided.
Mama san yakiniku
YouTube ChannelYouTube Channel
Also by Fumiya Sato
Mama-san Yakiniku
Who's watching?
Yuuchan, shiitake mushrooms are ready!
Shall I give them to you?
What? You sure?
Yes, it's okay.
I'll eat what you like, Yuuchan.
I'm so happy! Thank you!
You're happy?
Bamboo shoots!
We got shiitake mushrooms!
Delicious mushrooms!
What do you like about shiitake mushrooms?
Hmm?
The texture?
And the smell?
Mm-hmm? Smell?
Yes, I like the smell.
Shiitake mushrooms taste good when they're juicy, don't you think?
Yum!
From the inside.
Oh, this!
Juicy, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It almost came out of my mouth.
I can do it.
Yuuchan, eat it.
If I can get it out of my mouth, put a little mosaic on it.
How hungry are you? Right now.
What percentage?
Seven to eight?
I don't know... 8 minutes.
I think you're at your limit.I think he's reaching his limit, don't you?
I don't know. You don't think he'll eat it?
No, I'll eat it. I'll eat it.
It's just... when you eat it while talking to me, it's so sweet that it makes me curious.
Hey! I thought so!
It's really only about half of what I eat by myself.
I should be able to eat a little more.
You ordered the rice wine, didn't you?
I did.
You asked for a kiss, didn't you?
Chew.
You're gonna eat it?
Yeah, I'm gonna eat it.
What's in your stomach right now?
What?
Sleepy.
I ate a lot.
Yeah, I'm full.
Me too.
I ate.
Hey, don't open your nostrils.
It's okay.
I'm just gonna open my nostrils.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No more nostrils.
Yes, sir.
Soup just arrived.
I always end my favorite meal with soup.
That's right.
It's simple, but it's great.
It's hot.
What should I do?
Yum!Yum!
Glad to hear it, and the waitress too.
I'd like to finish you off with some ice cream.
Eat slowly.
I'll eat slowly when the cameras aren't rolling.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Sleepy, sleepy.
Sleepy. I'm so full.
Mmm.